I'm going to do a white eyeliner inside her eye.
We kind of smoked out the outside with the brown but I really want her eyes to pop, especially since it's got that orange.
I don't want it to be too dark and sultry so I'm going to use a white kohl eyeliner and it's just a soft eyeliner.
I'm going to line the inside of her eye and what that's going to do is it's really going to brighten her eyes and make it pop.
Just make sure you're very gentle.
Make sure your eyeliner is clean and just go very easy on the inside of the eye.
If you have a good liner, it's going to go on really nice and smooth and you'll be able to see that white right away.
And look so far at the difference between one and the other...it just really pops the eye.
And depending, you can add a little more, how bright you want it to be.
I'm sure we've all seen this white eyeliner.
And look at the difference by just adding a little bit of this eyeliner into the eye, what a difference this makes.
It just brightens the eye, one compared to the other.
And it just really accentuates that orange color.
This is great for photographic.
It's fine too, for going out.
But it's fantastic for photographic, I mean it's really just going to make that orange pop and make the eye look bigger and brighter.